qnetindia.net 2017-08-14

# QNET Direct Selling Company | Privacy Policy

## **Effective:** 18 December 2012   
**Updated:** December 2013

QNet Ltd. (also referred to as ‘QNET’, ‘we’, ‘us’ throughout this document), a member of the QI Group is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology to give you a powerful and safe online experience.

This Statement of Privacy applies to the QNET website [www.qnet.net](http://www.qnet.net/) and our mobile application, and governs data collection and usage. By using the QNET website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

The QI Group is an awardee of the prestigious TRUSTe's Privacy Seal, signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by one of the world’s leading privacy company, TRUSTe, for compliance with TRUSTe's privacy seal programme. Requirements for this programme include transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among global consumers and organisations, through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. The TRUSTe programme does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy statement or practices, please contact us at [privacy@qnet.net](mailto:privacy@qnet.net). If you are not satisfied with our response, you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe certification only covers information collected on [www.qnet.net](http://www.qnet.net/) and our mobile application, and/or any other means as will be notified from time to time and does not cover information that may be collected through other sites that may be owned and operated by us.

## Collection of Your Personal Information

QNET collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number and a pin. QNET also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP/Postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

QNET collects certain types of personally identifiable information from businesses such as company name, location address, contact person, position,  phone number, email address, valid ID document type and number, registered date of the company, and a pin.

We may collect information about third parties from you such as details of names, email addresses, and date of birth data. The information is requested for the purpose of nominating a beneficiary for your Representativeship with QNET or for shipping purposes. If your spouse or family members wish to have their information removed from our site, they may contact us at [privacy@qnet.net](mailto:privacy@qnet.net).

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by QNET. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by QNET for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the QNET website.

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who have access to them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@qnet.net](mailto:privacy@qnet.net). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

QNET encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from QNET so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. QNET is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content of websites outside of the QNET website and the QNET family of websites.

When you download and use our services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and device identifier (UDID).

We do not ask you for access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile applications or services.

## Use of Your Personal Information

QNET collects and uses your personal information to help you operate the QNET website and deliver the services you have requested, such as allowing you to keep track of new referrals, track shipments, orders and payments, account balances, transactions, activity and performance, commissions and your Global Support Centre (GSC). QNET also uses your personally identifiable information to respond to your enquiries, allow you to subscribe to RSS feeds, newsletters, articles, updates, and inform you of other products or services available from QNET and its affiliates. QNET may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinions of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. We may require you to provide us certain demographic information (such as zip code).  We will also use this information to monitor site traffic and personalise the site.

QNET collects and uses your personal information to create your business account and allow you to sell items on the site to individuals, delivering services you have requested. We may also use your information to send you relevant newsletters, respond to your enquiries, allow you to subscribe to RSS feeds, newsletters, articles and updates. To learn how you may opt-out/ unsubscribe from certain types of communications, please see the paragraph below.

QNET does not share, sell, rent or lease its customer information lists to third parties other than as disclosed in this privacy policy. QNET may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, name, address, telephone number) will not be transferred to the third party. In addition, QNET may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, process payments, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to QNET, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. If you no longer wish to receive email offers, newsletters, articles, or updates you may opt-out at any time by using the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication, or simply by emailing us at [unsubscribe@qnet.net](mailto:unsubscribe@qnet.net).

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, to protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

QNET does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

QNET keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within QNET in order to determine what QNET services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising within QNET to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

## Use of Cookies

The QNET website use cookies to help you personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programmes or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide convenient features to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise QNET's pages, or register with the QNET site or services, a cookie helps QNET to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses and so on. When you return to the same QNET website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the QNET features that you customised.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the QNET services or websites you visit.

The use of third party cookies is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

## Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ or our third party tracking utility partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the full stop at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

## Flash LSOs

We use local shared objects, also known as flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control, or display content based upon what you view on the QNET site to personalise your visit. Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of data and type of data used, and also because of how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for flash cookies click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118).  

## Mobile Analytics

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile app.

## Security of Your Personal Information

QNET uses best industry practices to ensure that it secures your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure and secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment., protected from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

QNET follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we have received it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Social Media (Features) and Widgets

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook ‘Like’ button and Widgets, such as the ‘Share this’ button or interactive mini programmes that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Testimonials

We post testimonials on our website which may contain personal information. We do obtain the customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from our testimonials, contact us at privacy@qnet.net. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Access to Your Personal Information

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, delete inaccuracies, or update them by selecting ‘My Profile’ once you have logged into your account or by contacting us at privacy@qnet.net. We will respond to your enquiries within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to keep providing you with our services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at the email address listed above.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Changes to this Statement

We may from time to time update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any changes which we deem to be material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address registered to your account) or by means of a notice on the QNET website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Information

QNET welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that QNET has not adhered to this Statement, please contact QNET's webmaster. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

**QNet Ltd**

Units G-L, 21/F, MG Tower

133 Hoi Bun Road, Kwun Tong Kowloon East, Hong Kong

**Tel:** +852 2263 9000

**Fax:** +852 2802 0981

**Email:  ** [global.support@qnet.net](mailto:global.support@qnet.net)
